[siren]
-Hey Chey.
-Chey, get up.
Chey, open your eyes.
Hey Chey.
[monitor beeping]
'While we're taking our
last breath artificially,'
'we don't remember about the money
we have in our bank account.'
'We don't remember how
many building we have.'
'Just, all our best memories flash
at once in front of our eyes.'
'As many memories flash,
we're like so much rich.'
'I too have some.'
[monitor beeping] [heart pounding]
'Few strangers enter into
everyone's life to add craziness.
everyone's life to add craziness.'
'We call them friends.'
'It's only them full of remembrances,
my best friends.'
'He's Dhruv.'
'Though he looks so strong
he is very sensitive.'
'He's the one who reacts first
whenever someone attacks our gang.'
'He's Bunty, the craziest from our gang.'
'He has a variety solution
for every problem.'
'He's Arya and he has more
knowledge than all of us.'
'He always keeps trying to live
every moment of life as he likes.'
'This is me.'
'All do call me as sweet and innocent.'
'That's why may be...'
'From childhood, my friends are taking
care of me not to feel as fatherless.'
"It is excitement, let's do mischief"
Though we four are different in looks
and what we do, our soul is one.
"It is excitement, let's do mischief"
'For the third class
marks we scored in 10th,'
'Our typical parents put us in
Vijayawada jail for studying well.'
'He's the jailor of that jail.'
[cheering]
'We don't get education in jail, right?
Thus we learnt all the rest.'
-Cheers!
-How's it, dude?
-How is it?
Is it good?
Hey, it's so tasty dude.
How's it?
-Maybe this is the Elixir.
-Give it here.
Wow! Wow!
Maybe this is why all uncles at my
house in the nights take a chilled beer,
forget their tensions and
jump happily like this.
True dude.
Hey, our Government should
supply beer instead of water.
Hey, leave all that. We all should
be together like this forever.
Yes dude.
In life, we should never fight or get
separated either for girls or for money.
Let's keep sipping beers and live happily
like this with no tensions for life long.
-Sure dude.
-Whatever problems we get or situations...
even if an earthquake comes,
we should be together like this forever.
-Promise.
Hurray!
That was the first beer
we had in our life.
With the kick on, we promised to
be together like this forever.
The confidence we got made us
jump over the College wall,
and took us till recording dance.
"This is a mass material and
whatever you like is yours"
"If you find some dark spot,
you'll try to reach it"
"Come on enjoy the country chicken"
"Come on, dance with pure mass steps"
"Show your power and
shake your whole body"
"Let the whole bottle give kick and dance"
Show the arrogance from me in you.
"I've taught lessons to many as you"
"Enjoy today and make some noise"
"Beat the drums, beat a bit louder"
"Let's beat today, beat with full energy"
"It's a blast now, show your energy"
"This is a mass material and
whatever you like is yours"
"Why in hiding, come on to the top"
Hey! It's our warden. Come let's go.
It's our warden. Please wait...
[shouts]
[pops] [liquid pouring]
HUSHARU.
Hey, go slowly. That watchman may see.
Ok, climb the wall slowly.
Hey, careful with the beer.
Nothing will happen to Beer,
I'm here right?
Hey, he's sleeping dumb.
-Looks like he had a quarter.
-Come on, let's go.
This is the last day of our B.Tech life.
We are going to enter into the real world.
Everybodies lives are going
to start from this stage.
Including our lives.
Not him dude,
we shall say that Sekhar Kammula first.
Yes dude,
that Happy Days film affected us badly.
There wasn't even a single girl
in our College like Tamannaah.
Hey, we've been in this same
college from four years.
Did at least any single
girl go flat for us?
Is it? What'll you do getting a girl?
What can I say when you ask directly?
To hell with your shyness!
Hey,
you'll have fun only till you get a girl.
You'll know the real
torture after you get her.
How's that dude?
-Give it here, once
-Why man?
Girls are like the bomb.
They look great from a distance.
And if we go close and say
relationship and my foot,
it's like lighting them
up and you get blasted.
Hey, go man!
Why did he become so bad like this?
True, dude.
-Damn!
Hey, if we too had studied well,
we too would've got a girlfriend.
Hey, it's the same syllabus
from our grandparents days
and the half-knowledge
lecturers teaching that.
And this College ruining the
brains we already have...
All in childhood say to become
a Scientist and Astronaut,
but all turn fools after growing big.
No idea how many more
would become fools now.
Four years, is gone a waste!
We shall remove this statue's head.
Why are you all stay here?
Why didn't you go for the interview?
We shouldn't go to these factories
manufacturing sheep, health gets ruined.
Come on bro,
you think I don't know about you?
They won't even let you inside the
gate for the backlogs you have.
What are you talking too much idiot?
You want the old debt or not?
-I need bro
-Then?
Hey dude
-What dude?
My job got confirmed.
Congrats bro,
we can now happily do the jobs.
-Right dude.
-We studied well and got the job.
-Hey Satish.
-Yes.
-How much is your salary?
-17K per month.
17K!
-And yours?
-Mine too is 17K per month.
Oh, which Company dude?
BELL.
They'll have to live life
long ringing the bell
-Hey, what's your percentage?
-85%
-Oh. Yours?
-63%
Are we both into the same
company with the same salary?
Hey, why do you waste talent for
just 15 to 20K paid by that Company?
Do something on your own
and you will get better.
Huh, you're advising us?
-Don't you wish to be going to the office?
-Hey, wait dude.
Why about these, move on man.
-You'll get bashed.
-These idiots will never get settled.
We should've hit them.
I'd have given two shots
if he'd spoken more.
-Leave it, dude.
-No, they should get it.
Hey, lecturer!
Shucks! Sir, dude...
If you hadn't wasted time
in smoking and studied well,
you too would've got good jobs
attending the interviews, right?
-You said well!
-Go sir, leave.
Fine,
but what does this lecturer teach us?
He is the M1 lecturer.
[bike starts]
Yes dude, he's the one who failed me.
[bike leaving]
Dude, clear that subject in this march.
-Hello brother.
-Yes.
You performed recently on an annual day,
right?
You played the guitar great, brother.
Okay, okay.
-Which year are you guys?
-First year, brother.
-First year?
-Yes, brother.
-Then what is that on the ear?
-Just like that, brother.
-Attitude?
-No brother.
Hey, being juniors won't you
make friends with seniors?
We will brother.
-And you?
-We will brother.
Come on, move then.
[oil popping]
[indistinct people chattering]
Cheers!
Hey,
why are you sipping Breezer like girls?
Hey bro, get two beers.
-Hey, order some stuff.
-Come on give the order.
Brother, bring boiled peanut.
-Hey idiot...
-Yes.
-He's the one who pays the bill.
-Oh!
Take the order...
Four Omelets, ten boiled eggs, three
Tanduri Chicken pieces, two breast pieces
and one plate boti and
five fish fry pieces.
-Brother...
-What dude? Do you need anything?
No brother.
Hey, give the bag.
Give it...
No brother.
-Hey, you give the bag man, give it.
-Hey, give the bag.
-How are the girls in class?
-They aren't good at all, brother.
-Brother, please no.
-Hey, you wait. See what's in there.
What's this tiffin box like a small kid?
It's Upma brother.
Hey Dhruv, you take this.
-Are Cashew nuts there in it?
-See...
What's this dude?
-Brother, please no...
-Greeting card?
Hey, see what's this.
I think it's a love letter.
Hey, what are these passes?
Costume party passes, brother.
Costume party, what is that?
That is, costume theme bro
like Superheroes, ghosts...
What language is he speaking, dude?
They come in the dress what they like,
brother.
This sounds like some fancy
dress competition, right?
-It's like the Halloween in the US, right?
-In a way like that, brother.
They drink full and
enjoy completely brother.
-Will there be girls?
-They will be, brother.
They will be super wearing short dresses.
You've advanced well, dude.
Thanks brother.
Hey, keep them in.
Brother, please...
Brother, please
-Hey, move.
-Hey, keep quiet.
-Brother, there are just 4 passes.
No problem dude, we too are just four.
Ok but are the passes including alcohol?
Bro, passes are only for the entry.
We shall buy everything inside.
Hey, enough of the introductions.
Go and pay the bill now.
Move now.
-Go and pay the bill.
-Move now.
Hey, get up and out.
Enough now, go to the class and sleep.
Get out guys.
Hey Dhruv,
get a carton of beers while you're back.
Why dude, we are going to a
party and we'll buy there.
Hey fool, one beer would cost 500 there.
We shall spend that amount,
drink full, go and
Aa what next...
We shall go there,
buy one beer and manage.
Bro, you are super and you're a God Bunty.
-Come on guys.
-Cheers.
We shall enjoy today.
Hey, we shall flirt with minimum
four girls in the party today.
We will but you don't
get out drinking fully.
Nothing so dude.
Why did this tailor stitch a single piece?
How to pee?
Yes dude, I too don't understand the same.
I'm full safe, I've got great comfort.
He's got full freedom.
[laughs]
-Oh damn!
-Hey, Chey's mom... Chey's mom!
Useless fellows.
No idea when do they let my son go.
[gasps]
The spider has arrived.
Oh no! Mummy!
He's caught.
What's this? Won't you change at all?
You always are with these waste
friends into roaming and drinking.
Isn't there anything in life, Chey?
Hey, won't you leave him
till he's completely ruined?
Go and do something useful.
-We're in the same thing now, right?
-Damn!
Thank God!
-Hey, what's this lecture man?
-Sorry dude.
-Come on, is this any new for us?
-Come on.
You take this beer.
Hey Dhruv, hold this.
This is a daily chore, take it easy.
[engine starts]
Hail Mahishmathi!
Cheers!
When there isn't craziness in life,
what's the use of that life?
-Kiss... Kiss...
[laughs]
I'd a wish from long
back to kiss Spiderman.
And I always wanted to
make out with an angel.
Let's kiss?
"Why don't you stay?"
"My heart is yours"
Muah... Muah...
What's he chewing in the air?
Did he have any adultered drink or what?
Muah... Muah...
What are you doing Spidy?
Cheers!
Hey, let's do bottom's up.
Hey bro, I liked a girl.
-I just saw her.
-Who, dude?
She came in white colour angel costume.
-She's so beautiful...
-Chey liked a girl.
-Who... who... who...?
-Where dude?
-There she is.
-Hey Chey.
-Come on.
-She's so beautiful.
-She is awesome.
Hey, do some thing guys.
Shall we flirt that adjacent girl?
Hey, I got a crazy idea.
Wait, I will arrange.
Hey waiter!
[club music]
Who gave it?
Thank you.
-Oh Damn!
-Hey!
-What the hell?
-Bro, it's bleeding.
Do you make such nonsense
for a small compliment?
-Take it easy.
-Ugh!
-You are finished.
-Arya...
You guys wait,
I'll go and teach him a lesson.
-Hey, you sit.
-Why did you hit him?
Excuse me, hold this.
Hey, hold this.
Hey!
How dare you to hit our friend, rascal?
-You stay right here.
-Go, rascal.
-Have you lost it?
-Yes.
[indistinct voices]
[groans]
[shouts]
[crowd shouting]
You...Idiot.
-You leave me
-Come you bloody...
-Come out let's see you outside.
[indistinct voices]
-You rascal...
-Idiot.
Guys, I thought to flirt with a
girl and enjoy the party happily.
What's that nuisance dude?
Damn!
His nose broke, you got slapped on
your cheek and he got a great punch.
There won't be anything
filthy than this dude.
Hey man, blow.
Hey, blow properly.
[blowing]
[device beeping]
Sir, record break! Meter reading is 236.
[indistinct voice in walkie talkie]
It's my dad's car, dude.
Hey, get down from the car.
Damn!
Sir, please Sir.
My dad is very strict Sir.
He would beat me up getting to know.
Please leave Sir.
You don't worry.
Go home like this, get your dad
and we shall directly talk to him.
Sir...
Hey, you wait dude.
Sir, SP Narayana Murthy is my uncle.
Is it dear? Very nice.
Call Sir once and we shall talk to him.
Give the keys.
-Constable
-Sir.
-Take the RC and seize the car.
-Ok Sir.
Plan special treatment as he
broke the record in meter reading.
Ok sir.
-Hey, move.
-Hey, who the hell is he?
My foot, don't I have another cigarette?
No idea how much should I get
scolded and beaten up by my dad.
Hey, keep the phone in.
Hold the board properly.
What are they saying, dude?
There's a Cricket match
in the evening it seems.
Ok, let's go then.
Come on, come on. [indistinct voices]
I'm still thinking
about that angel girl dude.
She'd have forgotten you long back.
Are you sure?
Still, why about that girl's mess for you?
Watch the match.
Oh, well played. [phone ringing]
No, no! Ok, ok!
Hi, who is this?
Hi, this is Riya.
Sorry, I don't know anyone named Riya.
You sent a note to me yesterday
with the waiter, right?
Oh God! Bro, that girl called.
-Who, customer care?
-No dude, that angel girl.
-Hey Riya.
-He's out now.
So, you saved my number.
How are you?
I'm doing good,
just the nose is a bit swollen.
Hey,
I'm so sorry for what that idiot has done.
Yes, it's ok.
You called me as he hit me, right?
I'd have called even if he hadn't hit.
Oh, cool.
You're a guitarist, right?
Yes, how do you know?
I got it when I searched your
name and phone number in FB.
Oh, cool.
I was thinking, learning to play
the guitar. Can you teach me?
-Yes, definitely.
-Perfect.
Arya!
Hey, Arya!
-Hey, Arya!
-Yes.
-Look here dude.
-Sorry, sorry.
Arya... Arya... Arya...
Hey, you hit the great shot, dude.
Come on Dhruv!
[indistinct voices]
-Hey Arya, run idiot.
-Hey, come on. Give the ball...
-Go dude, go...
-Hey, go dude...
Come on.
[stumped]
Howzzat?
-Damn!
-Umpire, it's out.
-Hey, umpire's decision is final.
[indistinct voices]
Hey, this guy too...
Whom are you placing hands on, rascal?
You put hands on me, idiot?
Rascal! [crowd shouting]
-That's a clean in, what are you seeing?
-That's in the air, that's out.
-I said umpire said, right?
-It's out of the crease.
-That's out, damn sure out.
-Wait, what's your nuisance idiot?
That's out.
-Out, right?
-Yes.
-Take it.
-That's what I'm saying, right?
You rascal... Hey...
I need a chocolate
Chocolate, ok. [crow caws]
No, no! I need vanilla. [crow caws]
Order only one.
-I need chocolate.
-Chocolate?
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
-Sure?
-Sure
-One chocolate.
-Do you need any chips too?
-Take it, madam.
-Take it.
-Excuse me...
Geetha!
"How did it happen?"
"Is this true or a dream?"
"I'm there like this"
"How did I transform like this?"
"The colours which weren't there before,"
"has touched the heart"
"The name of the magic which
doesn't have a medicine"
"It might be love"
"It's you..."
"You are always in me"
Oh my God, what happened to you?
What a transformation?
I can't believe this.
Come, come, come... Come on sit.
Where were you for so many years Geetha?
Entire happiness was gone
because of you in my life.
My Psycho dad put me in all
girls colleges after school.
No smart phone too.
He won't let me go anywhere.
He won't let me roam with anyone.
I should take this fatty along with me,
wherever I wish to go.
You eat dear.
My entire life has become a torture.
Why not search for positive even in this?
See how beautiful have
you become being at home?
I've come now, right? I'll show
you everything you missed in life.
Ok?
Huh, that isn't possible.
My dad won't let me go
anywhere from the house.
I'll take care of all that.
From now on,
your job is just to be happy, that's all.
For Arya,
his first love Geetha was seen again.
Whereas in my case,
a girl called me to her house directly.
[birds chirping] Hi.
Hi.
Aww! So cute.
-Sorry, sorry...
-It's ok, no problem.
Come on, let's go in.
Dad, this is my friend Chey.
-Hi uncle
-Hi Chey.
[birds chirping] I too wish to
learn Guitar, will you teach?
Yes, sure uncle.
-Riya, I'm going out dear.
-Yes, please come.
[guitar playing]
Which chord is this?
Chord D.
Oh, ok!
-And this one is...
-C Chord.
Nice.
Umm... Can I try?
-Yeah, sure.
-Yes!
[birds chirping]
Madam, coffee.
Yeah.
-Oh Damn!
-Take it.
"Where's The Party Tonight song
from the film Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna"
We never even dreamt right, that Arya
and Geetha will be together again.
It's all in the Lord of the rings man.
How did that Chey guy get such a hot girl,
man?
What's your problem, dude?
See there...
-That is life dude.
-Come on, eat.
Enough.
It'd have been so great
if we too had girlfriends.
-Hey, you need a girlfriend right?
-Yes.
There's a girl in every street of
Hyderabad and I'll set the date for us.
-How's that?
-Come.
Login to Tinder.
Boys set girls and the girls set boys
so easily for a date in this app.
There won't be any hi and bye in
this but just when, where. That's it.
Super Bunty, super. Set even for me dude.
If the girl is good, swipe right
and swipe left if she is not good.
They accept if they like.
Crazy Bunty, hey please set even for me.
Good, good, good and not good.
-Hey, she was good right?
-Should I set the date or you'll set.
You set it.
-No, you set it...
-No dude, please do it...
[phone beeping]
-Bro, a girl accepted immediately.
-You're great Bunty.
Set a girl even for me dude, please.
-Shall I ask to bring her friend too?
-Yes, please tell.
Hi, get your friend also.
We'll go for a double date.
[phone beeping]
Hey, what's the matter? Did she say ok? Is
her friend coming? Come on, tell Bunty...
It seems she shall pay Vodaphone bill.
Will you pay?
-Please pay for it.
-It's ok... no dude.
He's slowly getting heated up.
[phone beeping]
Bro, she says that she would
come for a date with her friend.
Hey, great Bunty. Bunty!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
[cicadas critter]
No one saw me, right?
Huh, how to climb man? Yes, here.
Psst!
Hi. [gasps]
What're you doing here?
My dad will kill if he sees.
Wow, see you look so
beautiful in this moonlight.
Will you make me sit right here
or will you let me come in?
Yes, come, come.
Huh!
Oh, did my six come till here?
Great!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Neighbours will see, sit down.
Hey, you don't take any tension.
None will see.
Still, I got you a gift.
Guess, what did I get?
-What?
-You'll be surprised.
Here...
What's this?
See...
You remember?
I should forget to remember, right?
-That's so sweet.
-Thank you.
Huh! The sky is so beautiful, right?
That moon, stars...
Actually, give your phone.
Why?
-Give the phone.
-Ok.
What are you doing?
See...
What's that?
-See.
-Oh my!
See our stars and our zodiac signs.
What, we can see even stars in this?
Yeah.
This is so crazy.
Actually, I like stargazing a lot.
-Ok.
-Our lives change...
...with these planets and their movements.
By any chance, would you say
something like horoscope?
Yeah.
I like palm reading very much.
Show me your hand.
You like palm reading?
-Say what all would we do now?
-Ok.
This line says we will
go for a long drive.
Ok.
This line says, we'll dance in the club.
You said so many lines, right?
Then what is this big line
saying we would do more?
What happened?
Riya, I've to leave.
-I can't teach you guitar any more.
-What's wrong?
I can't any more Riya.
Chai, what's this childish behaviour?
Tell me, what's wrong?
I don't know how to say this to you Riya.
Either I see you or touch,
something is happening inside me...
Especially that tattoo on your neck,
all my focus is going on to that.
I'm unable to concentrate at all.
Ok, ok!
Calm down... calm down...
Your eyes, your fragrance,
that style of pushing your hairs back...
It's all driving me crazy.
I'm unable to concentrate at all.
It's better for me and you, I'll leave.
"Why not stay back?"
[indistinct music]
-Bro.
-Yes.
We get fair with this cut fruit
facial, right? [radio playing]
-"Kanulanu Thaake song from Manam movie"
-Yes, bro.
We should shine.
With the same hand,
apply if you have some whitewash too, bro.
-The boy should shine very fair.
-You stay calm, bro.
Hey Bunty, I'm great excited and
a bit scared at the same time too.
Why dude?
If those girls are horrible
unlike in the photos,
what's our situation dude?
Get up once.
Idiot, we'll go there and see the girls.
We'll take them on a date if they're good.
If they aren't good looking then act
if you are attacked with Asthma.
What?
[panting]
Saying Oh God,
something happened to my friend,
let's escape from there.
-Simple.
-Bunty, you are super.
Urgh! Damn!
What are you like this, dude?
[radio playing]
What's wrong, just the face pack, right?
Damn, sit down. "Radio: Gallo
Telinattunde song from the film Jalsa"
[mouthing song]
Hey Bunty,
I'm very excited thinking about the date.
Super Bunty, you're great.
-What's this, you still didn't remove?
-Hey, don't touch that.
[honking] What happened?
-Do you know how much is that?
-How much?
-Rs. 8000 dude.
-Rs. 8000?
-Yeah.
-So what?
I bought it today, go for a date and
return it tomorrow.
Bro Bunty, you're super.
You're a God, that's all.
Hey, I think we've come.
Hey, there's a meter in the dashboard.
Give it here, once.
[blowing]
37 means manageable come on move.
[honking]
Where did you get this from?
Do you remember, we got caught
in drunk and drive last time?
-Umm... Is it on the costume party day?
-I picked up there.
Bro,
you're in crazier form than Virat Kohli.
Come on, move. Let's go in the
same flow and make the girls lie down.
[indistinct music]
-Bro...
-Yes.
-I recently read a survey.
-About what?
In between 20 to 25 years of age, we
should do 122 times sex per year it seems.
If not, health gets spoilt, you know?
122...
Hey, maybe that is the reason
I feel very weak these days.
It won't be from now dude. Still, thanks
to you. Girls are coming because of you.
I'm saying from today, our game starts.
We shall play dude, we shall play well.
Hurray!
Why are they not still coming dude?
It's time and they should be here by now,
right?
-Hey. See they are coming.
-Is it them?
-Hey wow.
-Set your dress.
-Hey, they're in no way like in photos.
-Why are they so bad dude?
Come on dude, let's go away.
Start it dude, start it.
[panting]
-Hey, are you ok?
-Madam, are you ok?
[panting]
Sruthi, what's wrong?
What happened?
They look like Hippopotamus and why
are they doing like this by seeing us?
To hell with our life!
My friend is got Asthma attack,
somebody help.
-She'd get.
-Help!
When she is so fat like a drum what else
would she get other than Asthma attack?
She's drum idiot.
You say me a drum idiot?
You look like a bear, you rascal.
How do you know that my
friend's name is that?
-Hey!
-It's known by just looks.
Hey, Buffalo won't become a
cow when it is coloured white.
She is also similar to that.
You say me a buffalo, rascal?
-Hey, my blazer dude...
-It's 8000...
Hey Bunty, come on dude
Who's this in between?
[glass breaks]
-Hey run fast, faster.
-Hey...
Hey caught me dude.
-Look at him.
-Hey, it will tear...
It ripped.
Hey my hand, dude.
-Hey bunty come fast.
-Come fast.
Hey, he is coming dude.
Run fast.
God, won't you show mercy at all?
What sin have I done?
Give me just one girlfriend, please.
For the insult faced in double date,
Dhruv just believed Facebook.
Damn! Damn!
What's this God, what are these
fake profiles? Will anyone do so?
Get me a good original girl, my God.
I'll take great care of her.
Please don't do so.
[gasps]
Soumya Reddy accepted your friend request.
Is she from Mumbai! No problem, the
girl is so nice. [laptop beeps]
Hi! What do you do?
Television: Till it turns into brownish.
This great lady watches the cookery
shows on TV for the whole day,
but always does the same roasted Dosa.
Pulihora with yesterday's rice and
the same dal and ladyfinger.
Damn!
Yes, go to your daughter's
house and she cooks you well.
Bunty! Bunty!
I'm working hard daily for day and night
and bringing you food at your mouth.
Yes.
Even to the office, I go
wearing only 400 rupees shirt.
You're grown up like a donkey.
You roam whole night with your waste
friends and get up at 12 in the noon.
You want 8000 worth
suit for your damn face,
and tearing the same too in just one day.
Dad, you just go to the office and thus
400 worth shirt is enough for you.
But I roam out for the whole day. Many
people do meet me and many keep seeing me.
-And thus is this blazer for me.
-What's so important work for you, man?
You can't understand even if I say you,
dad.
This great lady serves me the
leftover curries from the night.
-and a coat worth 8000 for him?
-Exactly.
Chapathi in buttermilk!
Will anyone eat?
God! I'm into a video chat
with Soumya for the first time.
Please, make her be very beautiful.
I'm saying, from now I won't do any sins,
be good and become a good guy. Please God!
One, two, three...
Are you going for any job interview?
Six... Job!
Damn, nothing as such.
Seven, eight, nine.
Please God.
[laptop beeping]
Hi.
One minute Soumya,
one minute, one minute!
My God, you're great and you exist.
Thank you God!
Yes! Yes!
I never drank
-What, you never had a beer?
-No.
-Never had a beer in a lifetime?
-What are you saying?
You know what you're missing out on?
Yuck!
-Have one sip.
-No.
I'm saying right?
Have one sip.
-It's crazy, right?
-Actually, it's not that bad.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
-Arya, I want to go to a club and dance.
-Get up and I'll tell.
"The feet walked on the moving clouds"
"Heart has jumped like a Dragonfly"
"Life has smiled so like never before"
"Let's do these wonders Like making
them go thousand times bigger"
"Do you mean me?"
"Is my heartbeat yours?"
"I'll fill in you"
"I'll be with you even
after my breath stops"
"The feet walked on the moving clouds"
"The age danced like
the shining firefly"
"I saw with lips and smiled with eyes"
"Every second is a
wonder as you're with me"
"Though the whole world
stops and looks at us"
"Let's dont care and leave
floating in another world"
"Do you mean me?"
"Is my heartbeat yours?"
"I'll fill in you"
"I'll be with you even
after my breath stops"
"Heart took the first
steps with you like this"
"No idea why sleep doesn't
approach like this"
"Let's break all distances
between us like threads"
"Let's capture the time once in the fist"
"Do you mean me?"
"Is my heartbeat yours?"
"I'll fill in you"
"I'll be with you even
after my breath stops"
"The feet walked on the moving clouds"
"Heart has jumped like a Dragonfly"
"Life has smiled so like never before"
"Let's do these wonders Like making
them go thousand times bigger"
Baby, I think this is life.
We shall own this all in future.
Yes, totally.
-Let's go to US.
-What?
Yes, let's go to US.
Let's first do Masters there
and then settle there doing jobs.
-I'll take care of everything.
-What?
I had a dream from
childhood to settle in the US.
All my cousins are right
there and leading a Royal life.
-Baby...
-Yes.
Are you hungry?
No.
-If not, are you on your periods?
-No
Then why are you talking crazy like this?
What crazy, I'm talking with clarity.
If you're here, you will be unfit for
anything like your waste friends.
Why did they come in between now?
Ok, leave about them.
What'll you do being here?
I'll do something.
Settle down fast or else we'll move to US.
Arya, you earn about 15000 per month.
Yes.
I'll sell my paintings
and earn about Rs. 10000.
We can live happily with that Rs. 25000.
We shall spend Rs. 20000 from that Rs.
25000 for your shopping and cosmetics.
-Is it ok?
-Love you baby.
Fine Arya,
we'll be the same forever, right?
My dad will accept you, right?
Geetha, suffering on one
side thinking about the past,
and fear on the other thinking about
future, you're ruining the present.
See, how beautiful is the moment?
Hey, enjoy and treasure it.
-Cherish every moment.
-Are you sure?
Yes.
[machine hissing]
-Hey.
-Hi Baby.
Hi.
-What's this?
-One second.
See, how good your name looks on my hand.
Yes, it's very good.
So, I'm completely yours now.
Cool.
-You too have my name, come on.
-What?
-Come on, nothing will happen.
-No, I won't.
-No, sit. Nothing will happen.
-Riya please, I'll get in later.
-Baby, nothing happens.
-Nothing will happen.
-Wait bro.
-Please, please.
-Hey, mom is calling. She even called me.
-Hello bro.
-Go later, nothing happens.
-I got to go, have urgent work.
-It takes just two minutes bro.
-Nothing happens.
-You hold on.
Actually, I'm allergic to
needles and I shouldn't have it.
I get swelling all over the body.
So, you don't like me...
-Nothing so Riya.
-Then get it done.
Bro, nothing happens.
Mummy!
Tell me about yourself.
Madam, I don't want money.
You are so beautiful.
Why are you hesitating for this?
Everyone talks askew.
You look like a straight forward guy.
-Dude.
-Yes.
-What do they call when four do together?
-Foursome.
-Three.
-Threesome.
-And two.
-Awesome.
I finally understood dude,
why all call me handsome...
Yes bro, none would be as handsome
as you in the whole of twin cities.
See there, dude.
-Hey, see those views.
-That's why our population grew so much.
Yes, maybe!
[door shuts]
What happened dude?
Hey, I lost a lot of blood.
Aww! so cute.
They pierced many needles.
-Is it like this?
-Ouch!
-Hey, he'll die.
-Oh God!
That is the reason we say
not to mess with the girls.
Yes!
Looks to be a stupid psychopath,
will anyone do so?
Hey, she is talking rubbish.
She says, I should settle down fast
else she would take me to the U.S.
-What does the settlement mean?
-Is it about earning money?
I think so.
Hey, you need money now right?
Yes.
-We'll take care of that, ok?
-Ok.
Fine. Come on, come...
good hot scene is on.
So, what's my role?
God has just created you.
[crow]
-Huh!
-Hmm...
You're looking at each
other for the first time.
-Some unknown great shiver in the body.
-Hmm...
-A wish to touch each other.
-Ahh!
Slowly touching like that...
Slowly...
Carry on in the flow...
-Sounds interesting.
-Hmm...
Rasikaraja productions,
Screams in the forest, scene 1, take 1...
-Action!
-Be depressed.
You aren't understanding anything at all.
Not knowing where you're
too, same ways, a sad face...
Look up at the God...
Why God, your count
16000, my count why not even 1?
You suddenly saw a girl there.
Finally God showed mercy
and sent a beautiful girl.
Give a smile.
Bite the apple sexily.
Turn it, turn... right!
Get up slowly!
Carry that smile, smile... Yes, exactly.
Hit that stick to the ground...
Hang holding the rope like
Tarzan to impress that girl.
Come on Tarzan dear, did
you hold the rope? Hold it.
[tarzan yelling sound]
[music]
Tarzan dear,
approach first and then give touch.
You touched so, both go down...
Slowly, yes slowly...
Bro, put the top angle...
Perfect thumbnail shot...
Now apply Zandu Balm...
Zandu balm... Zandu balm...
Zandu balm for pain... Come on...
Jungle queen 2 entry...
Come on enter...
Tarzan dear, iron jungle queen...
Same way in flow, carry on...
Come on Tarzan dear,
perfect shot and take ok!
[camera buzzes]
Come on, let's go to US.
I'll take care of everything.
Hey, no need of all
that. I can't come to US.
What's there in India?
Mom is here,
Hyderabad and my friends are here.
There'd be 100 people here to
wish once I step out from the house.
I can't lead the lonely life there.
But we can lead Royal life there.
We can happily do 9 to 5 job,
can earn in Dollars, can go for
world tour and can stay in a big house.
We can be happy even in single
bedroom flat when there's love.
Damn!
-Say, what exactly happened?
-What is your goal in life?
Goal!
I should do some work in the day,
I should have a beer with
them in the evening and laugh.
I should eat what mom cooked
in the night and then love you.
-That's all?
-That's all.
[blipping]
Take!
-What's this dude?
-Go and enjoy full with your girl.
[chuckles]
Where did you get so much money dude?
[sighs]
See this video.
[tarzan yelling sound]
[chuckles]
Hey, have you done this video?
Hmm...
[laughs]
It's super dude.
[laughing]
This video crazily became viral and
all the guys watching are banging on it.
[chuckles]
-Our creativity is so.
-Yeah!
I'm saying right
comments are it's next level.
Many thanks dude.
If friendship is a Cricket match,
you're Sachin and you're Sehwag in that.
Go idiot,
will you make us cry now or what?
No dude, really.
We'll do anything for you, dude.
"Why not stay back..."
"Heart is yours..."
"Why not hug..."
"Me to your heart..."
"Oh no!"
"Feet says not to stop on earth"
"It's floating again and again,"
"In the air like cloud"
"If beauty is a girl,"
"It's like being you"
"Said no hesitation,"
"To ask for a hug"
"Why not stay back..."
"Heart is yours..."
"Why not hug..."
"Me to your heart..."
"After seeing you like
the moon in darkness"
"Heart, felt happy and rose like a tide"
"I'm in some trance"
"I'm not in myself"
"In burning Sun"
"I never saw moonlight before"
"Like a shadow even in the dark,"
"When I'm with you"
"Why another birth for me?"
"This moment with you is enough"
"If beauty is a girl,"
"It's like being you"
"Said no hesitation"
"To ask for a hug"
"Why not stay back..."
"Heart is yours..."
"Why not hug..."
"Me to your heart..."
[phone rings]
-Hello!-Riya!
-What happened?
-What's wrong?
Why are you calling so many times?
-Check your phone once.
-What?
See how Chey and his friends,
-Are making worst videos.
-Who's calling at this time?
Come back...
-Leave me!
-What happened?
-What's wrong, come on.
-Leave my hand!
What happened? Ah!
What the hell is that?
-Oh damn! Damn!
-Are you out of your mind?
You are not kids anymore Chey.
-What is wrong with you?
-Hey, they did this for social purpose.
Social purpose! Do you have any sense?
Please Riya, come on let's go.
See how great this weather is.
Why for such a small thing, Riya please.
Don't touch me.
Argh! What's wrong with you?
I'm saying to come with me to US
and that I'll take care of everything,
but you're making all such porn videos.
What the hell?
Argh! You're coming back there again?
Did you bring me out with this money?
-Riya please listen to me once, Riya.
-Will you come to US with me or not?
It's good here, right?
All friends are here.
Chey, I'm asking you for the last time.
You want your friends or me?
Please Riya, listen to me.
-Chey, I'll go to US.
-Please Riya...
-I can't be here.
-Hey! Please...
Don't call me after going to Hyderabad.
Please Riya, give me one last chance.
I'll keep you very happy,
forget all these.
We shall lead very comfortable
life. Please Riya, listen to me.
Stay away!
Bro, we shall do something
otherwise Riya will leave to US it seems.
That idiot has come to separate
us. Still what did you like in her?
That curved face and fat nose.
She's waste dude, she's a devil.
-Hey, it's not good.
-She and her dirty acting.
She always comes up with some new
demands. We earn money somehow.
Why for her instead to eat
what we feed and sleep?
Hey, I'm saying you
don't say anything about her.
[indistinct music]
She's bent you so as you surrendered so.
Still she always keeps saying so
cute... So cute... Cute my foot!
Hey, there's a girl in
every street of Hyderabad,
I'll set a good girl
for you within a week.
No man, big salute to you and your setting
-Hey, shall we do any new video?
-Man, big salute to your videos.
Yes!
What, a strike?
-Crazy!
-Hey!
-Do some job dude.
-All these jobs aren't good for me.
ohh!
-Ok, will you do some business then?
-Where do we have so much money dude?
Even if we have, to set it up and run
successfully it takes minimum six months.
Then, what will you do man?
We don't have any
special talents too in us.
Talent should be in the blood.
See Ramcharan,
he dances so great in rhythm.
-There's batting in Kohli's blood
-What's in your blood then?
I don't about his blood but
there's HIV in Dhruv's blood.
You dad has HIV, rascal.
Ok, will you become a sperm donor then?
[chuckles]
Hey, all say job but a cab driver
earns more than the software guy today.
So basically, we don't have any rule to do
only job but we can even drive a cab, ok?
-Yes.
-Say dude.
-Yes, we'll drive cab. Best!
-Yeah!
-Where do we have a car, dude?
-Car...
Your Benz is there, right?
Yes, drive that Benz.
Anyways dad drinks two pegs and sleep's.
-Yeah!
-And it'd be free after that.
-You can drive then.
-Crazy dude, what else?
Yes dude, we can drive in the nights.
Hmm...
-Yea! What else dude?
-Let's move dude.
-Smile at least now dude.
-Bunty! Look at that girl.
[car engine starts]
[phone rings]
I'm really sorry Riya, please call me.
Shucks!
Pay with PayTM.
[door knocks]
Uncle, will you please call Riya?
Riya isn't home dear,
she has gone out on consultancy work.
-Any problem Chey?
-When'd she come back uncle?
Don't know dear, maybe she'd get late.
Argh!
[car honks]
[phone rings]
[dog barks]
See him driving a cab,
is this called to become responsible?
We'll be in US by this time tomorrow.
I was calling even you for the party.
But who'd drop us in cab?
What do you say Riya? Right Riya?
[laughing]
Hey, Surya... come here.
Someone is calling you.
-Someone
-Hey, hi bro.
Crazy party bro.
-Chey, that is...
-Do me a small help Riya.
Don't talk anything for some time.
Just stand there till I leave.
I want to remember all this.
-What do you wish to remember?
-Such never happened to me, Riya.
-What didn't happen?
-My heart breaking.
"I did a mistake believing you,"
"I'm going away with open eyes"
"Like breathe stops and life goes,"
"Your cheating is so"
"Like the fire hidden in the fist,"
"Is the time spent with you..."
"Tears aren't rolling down"
"There isn't a way to drive away the pain"
"I understood today
that forgetting is so easy"
"By seeing you"
"Isn't there a way to heal,"
"The wound done by the time?"
"Piercing a thorn in my heart,"
"You killed me so"
"I can't say out,"
"the sorrow with you..."
-Doctor!
-Ward boy!
Hey, he looks thin but is
like a buffalo to carry.
Is he any Devadasu,
drinking as his girl left him?
Hey, hold the hand.
He cut his hand and
fainted seeing his own blood.
Go on, come on go on
Oh no!
Would he break the car when given?
I've been saying from first
not to get into girls mess.
Our guys won't
understand unless experienced.
He ruined gang's prestige.
Excuse me Sir...
-Hello...
-Yes!
-Sir... Here.
-Huh?
Take it.
-Hey, Arya!
-Yes!
See this bill dude.
Hey, this isn't ours dude.
Hey, it's of Chey.
Hey, what's this bill?
Why did the hospital guys loot like this?
Go and call that Doctor.
-Doctor.
-Come on, call him.
-Hey, Doctor.
-Where is this fellow?
-What is this? Is this a bill or what?
Are all your private hospitals like this?
Will anyone bill
40,000 for a small hand cut?
What's this cheating, man?
Your friend has
anaplastic astrocytoma condition.
-What?
-There's a tumor in the brain.
-That means?
-Cancer!
It was all because of you.
He became unfit for
anything in his career.
He became mad going behind a girl.
Now, he got cancer.
Won't you leave him till he dies?
Damn!
Doctor,
did that injury cause him get cancer?
That injury actually helped.
We could diagnose cancer because of that.
Why did he actually get cancer, sir?
There are so many reasons.
Even Chai's father died from brain tumour
and so this can even be a hereditary case.
Sir, how about treatment now?
We need advanced chemotherapy treatment.
It would slowly destroy
the tumour and its cells.
So, there are 80% of
chances for him to recover.
What about the remaining 20%?
If tumour aggravates,
we'll have to perform a surgery and
remove the tumour as a last option.
And we can't even guarantee
five per cent success rate.
Moreover, we'll have to bring down doctors
from the USA to perform that surgery.
It might cost more than 30 lakh rupees.
But first, inform the
patient that he got cancer.
Hey, what shall we do now dude?
Madam, go and pay the bill
immediately at the counter.
Hey, he should recover at
the chemotherapy stage itself.
You are right dude. If not, where do
we get 30 lakhs for the operation?
How do we say this matter to Chey, dude?
Hey, you don't get tensed
and make him get tensed.
Hey, we shall handle in a cool way. Okay?
[door unlocks]
[machine beeping]
Hey chey!
-Chey, what're you doing?
-Are you bored?
You're taking good rest
and enjoying, aren't you?
Hey, what's wrong with me?
They put me in a hospital for
so long for such a small cut.
Nothing dude. It is normal.
You just got a small disease.
Disease?
What disease?
You had drinks in the pain
that girl left you, didn't you?
Okay. So?
-So...
-You got cancer it seems.
Cancer?
Hey, give up drink and cigarette first
and take healthy food and medicines.
It'll be cured.
Hey, don't you worry much.
The doctors told that it will
get cured within three months.
Will I die, dude?
Hey, it's unlike olden times.
Now, there's a cure for cancer.
What about my mom's situation, dude?
Hey, don't you be tensed.
The doctor clearly
explained everything to your mom
that you'd get cured and
nothing would happen to you.
Hey, a lot of people used to die
for small diseases at earlier times.
Such as typhoid, TB etc.
But now, just one injection is
enough and everything gets cured.
Yes dude, it's unlike earlier times.
There are plenty of advanced
treatments available out there.
What treatment, dude?
Keematherapy (Chemotherapy)
You stop it, idiot.
It is chemotherapy.
-Shut up rascal!
-Shall I tell you something?
Though Yuvraj Singh had lung cancer,
he considered it as if
some kind of viral fever
and won the trophy for India by
playing in the world cup, didn't he?
This is also the same thing.
You just don't bother and take it easy.
Hey, one out of every four guys
is getting cancer these days.
However, you're the good person
amongst our four-membered gang
and thus you got it.
-You're the good guy.
-That's all
Anyhow, would anybody drink in the
pain in the pain that a girl left?
Look at yourself,
Your face is like the guy from the tobacco
Ad which gets played before a movie.
Hey, we shall film an Ad for
our fellow love failure friends
to make them not to
get into this situation.
-Yes, we shall do
-It's crazy, dude!
-Shall we do it?
-Yes, we will.
Tell me.
Come on, tell me.
-Smile dude, come on
-Shall we do that or not?
-We shall do it.
-Yes!
What's wrong with these youngsters?
Love failures on one side
and unemployment on the other side.
Why doesn't anyone
open up their mouth?
We shall put an end to the negligent
behaviour of these girls.
My name is Chey.
I was in a deep love
with a girl for an year.
Our love started from dubsmash on
phone and went till tattooing on the hand.
Even then, she went to
the US by leaving me.
Perhaps, I may not love
any other girl again.
My aunt had to sell her two bangles.
Love, love and love!
They are deadly.
Boys, don't fall in love.
Don't let anyone fall.
'Those who search and get back the smiles
that left you, the beliefs you forgot,'
'and the forgotten courage are friends.'
[indistinct people chattering]
I thought to ask money
for Chey's treatment,
but why did all these people
come to give a lecture to me?
[sighs]
Arya, cool! Cool!
Hi Arya. Your brother bagged
a seat in IIT, Hyderabad.
Your dad is hosting such a big party.
Why did you arrive so late?
Well, what are you doing now?
I'm doing, doing...
You know,
my son is working for Cisco as a Manager.
I'll ask him and place
you up in a good job.
Thank you uncle.
But no thanks. I don't need this job.
Any reason?
I don't want to do a
job which I don't like
and keep dying every day for
lifelong like your son, uncle.
What are you saying, Arya?
Respect your elders.
You always say respect your elders,
respect women and so on.
Don't we have respect?
Won't we get that? Aren't we humans?
Arya!
You don't pull us into the competition
you created to satisfy your egos, dad.
My son is earning so much,
saved so much,
built a big building,
my son went for a foreign trip...
Lives are going haywire here
going for such boastings.
Look at your language, Arya.
All your peers have
settled in good positions.
You haven't started your career yet.
What exactly are you
thinking to do in life?
Taking birth, growing up, working
and again giving birth,
growing kids up, and then dying,
Is this what life's all about?
I wish to lead a happy life.
I don't want to get sacrificed to
the pressure created for this society
Arya, it is my last wish
to see you doing a job.
Huh, get away!
Job, my foot! Killing me...
-Arya!
-Come here
What happened, Arya?
I'm in a bit of frustration,
please cooperate.
Arya, I want things like sex and other
things to be explored only after marriage.
I can't do it now.
[glassware breaks]
Damn!
[knocking door]
Geetha!
[knocks]
Open the door
Crap!
[knocks]
Geetha!
Geetha! Open the door, dear.
What's do you want at this time, dad?
One of my books is missing, dear.
I came to see whether it's in your room.
Why would your book be in my room, daddy?
I came to your room in
the afternoon, dear.
Why would it be in the bathroom, dad?
There isn't anything here, dad.
Who the hell are you?
Come out.
How dare are you, rascal?
It is not your mistake.
She is to be blamed.
She ruined my reputation by falling
in love with someone in 10th standard.
And now, she brought someone into
the room and ruined my reputation again.
Don't feel very bad, uncle.
It was me whom she
loved in the tenth standard.
Won't you leave us?
However, why should we talk to you?
Come on, rascal.
Dad...
-If I ever see you around my house,
-Please leave him, dad.
I'll call the police
and get you thrashed.
Get lost!
'All my friends were drowned in grief.'
On one side, they're trying to save me
'and on the other side, they are being
tormented in their family problems.'
Hey Bunty, please switch off the AC.
The electricity bill is touching the sky.
Dad, I'm getting burned in this heat.
Please, try to understand.
[water rustling]
[birds chirping]
Chey isn't responding to the chemotherapy
treatment that was done till now.
What's it Doctor?
He is getting timely treatment, right?
Doctor,
please check the report one more time.
We checked everything. The size of
the tumour isn't shrinking at all.
We're able to control even the
tumour cells only with chemotherapy.
There's an expert doctor in the US.
We shall get him here and
get the operation done.
How much would that cost, doctor?
Approximately 30 Lakhs.
Why is the main hall so cool?
Hey donkey, why are you
sleeping like that? Get up!
My diabetes medicines
would get spoiled for heat.
Get up, get up you waste fellow.
What's your nuisance in
the morning, grandpa?
Who the hell would sleep by keeping
his head in the refrigerator? Get up.
Grandpa... Grandpa!
Keep your butt too in it, waste fellow?
-The old man is getting paranoid with age.
-Huh!
What happened to all the money
which invested in that project?
That is,
The new Government has shut down
that scheme citing it to be impractical.
Oh no! The mill is gone and
even the money invested is gone.
We didn't get even a single penny
-and the 5 years time got wasted. [clanks]
-Ah!
It's my ill-fate.
I'm not even left with the Mangalsutra.
Why are you fighting like that?
My property is there, right? Use that.
Yes, it's there!
What's your property dad?
What do you have?
Broken cot, old iron trunk...
Are you talking about those things?
They are in good condition, right?
Koteswara Rao... Koteswara Rao...
It's been six months since you paid rent.
I'll pay it, sir.
The new month has started.
Will you pay in this month at least?
Well, you can't pay it.
Vacate the house.
If I don't pay by the end of this
month, we'll definitely vacate, sir.
-This is the last warning.
-Okay, sir.
You'll be spared if you
pay the rent this month.
Otherwise, your things will
be thrown out of this house.
Okay, sir.
I can't live in a house
which is smaller than this.
Well, we will take you
to a very spacious house.
Your dad's house is having
just two rooms, isn't it?
Why my dad's house?
We'll send you to old age
home and you can be there.
[sighs in anger]
[thud]
-Where are you going, grandpa?
-To the toilet, will you come?
Damn, you nasty grandpa...
[slams door]
What's he doing inside?
[screams]
[thud]
What's might have happened?
-Dad
-Grandpa [knocks]
What are you doing inside?
Open the door daddy. [knocking]
Daddy...
[gasps]
Won't you even let me die peacefully?
[weeping]
Just you stop that crying.
I'll break your jaw.
I'm seriously asking Arya,
will you marry me or not?
I'm in a very big tension.
I can't marry you now.
My dad was correct that you've
been simply passing time with me.
That's why he got the
best guy as my life partner.
His name is Rahul and earns a
salary of 1 lakh rupees per month.
Did he find him?
Good, go and marry Rahul idiot.
Sorry, marry Mr Rahul.
How much, one lakh?
Live happily and luxuriously as
an ideal couple with that salary.
And we'll get rid of the crap!
What? Rid of the crap?
Yes, it is the best thing!
I'll marry Rahul. You're a waste fellow.
Go and marry that guy. Just go.
Don't call again.
[phone rings]
Yes Bunty, tell me.
Hey, I'm unable to bear the tension dude.
There's just one solution for all these.
We should have beer.
[traffic]
Hey... We thought to get relieved of
the tensions by having chilled beer,
But, what is this mess dude?
There's just 5 minutes left
for this store to get closed.
That's the reason for this rush.
Let's go there.
-Hey move...
-Just move guys...
-Hey Bunty, take it
-You idiot!
Hey Bunty...
Hey... Argh!
-Bunty, make it fast.
-Give 10 beers, bro.
Hey...
Please Brother...
Give 10 beers... 10 beers...
Bunty, get them fast dude.
There isn't any time.
[roller shutter closing]
Hey...
-Hey Bunty, look out the shutter.
-Give them quickly, bro.
Give them quickly, bro.
-Ah!
-Crap!
Ah!
Brother, my friend got stuck.
Lift the shutter, bro.
Hey Bunty, careful.
[screams]
Bunty...
Hey Bunty!
Mommy!
Please... Down the shutter bro.
Please...
Brother, my friend is stuck.
Bring down the shutter.
Bunty...
Hey... Dhruv!
[ears ringing]
Hey Bunty!
Hey, I tried very hard dude.
Damn,
I didn't get even one beer.
Hey, you don't take any tension.
We'll definitely but the
beer and drink it at home.
Hey, he is here.
Bro, we need three beers.
I have two beers.
-How much?
-500 rupees
500?
500? Why 500?
Why 500?
Well, make it 600 then.
Bro, give two for 500.
[siren]
The police are arriving...
-Hey, police dude!
-Come on, quickly get on the vehicle.
Hey, move...
[siren]
Hey, start it quickly.
They're coming.
Hey, start it dude.
Hey, the battery is down.
-Push it, dude. Make it quick.
-Zip it!
Move it, fast.
[siren]
Hey, they are here dude.
Kickstart it.
Hey, stop the vehicle.
Where did you get beers at this time?
They are mine, sir...
-Give that beer to me
-No, I won't give
-Give here, idiot
-I won't give
-You won't listen to words.
-Push fast.
-You should take the hit.
-Mommy!
-Hey, push... Push...
-Start the engine...
-Quickly push...
-Ouch!
-It's not getting started.
Hey, he's hitting me...
[bike engine starts]
Get on the bike, the vehicle started.
Keep going...
Damn you!
Ouch!
[bottle shatters]
Why is God very hard on us?
Won't he bless us?
Why does he have so much anger on us?
I think we are born at the worst time.
You are right dude!
When we wish to have a chilled beer
to forget all tensions for some time,
Even that's not working out.
Huh! The quality of
beer over here is waste.
One of my friends went to Europe
and brought the beer they manufactured.
Drinking one such beer is enough,
You'll have instant harmony and
it feels like you're in heaven.
Would it be so tasty?
Just one beer is enough
But still,
how would they manufacture that?
Hey idiot, what exactly is a beer?
-What?
-Wheat
Wheat?
Yes, it is made up of wheat.
They put some bacteria that is used
in making bread and add beer flavour.
That's it
-Is it that easy?
-Then, what did you think man?
In Europe, people won't be standing
in a line to buy beer unlike here
where we feel getting one beer as equal
to winning Kabaddi World Cup for India.
In Europe, they prepare their
own beer and get chilled.
Hey, shut up! How do they make
beer so easily? I won't believe it.
-Hey...
-He won't believe anything without proofs.
Show him.
See dude...
He's a kid, dude.
[indistinct audio from the mobile]
Did the police hit you very hard, dude?
They blasted my back, dude.
It is swollen.
Didn't he get beaten?
Bro, what if we make our own beer?
[music]
[door opens]
[birds flapping]
[bird flapping]
[grinding stone screeching]
Hey... Basically, there will
be six steps in brewing beer.
The first step is milling.
[burbles]
In this step, we shall soak
the wheat for the entire night.
They get sprouts by the morning.
That is called the Malt.
They should be dried in
the morning and ground.
The step 2 is mashing.
In mashing,
we should put the ground pulp in the
first container and boil it in hot water.
The step 3 is called lottering.
The boiled liquid should be...
...taken into the second container
by separating it from the pulp.
The hops are to be mixed in that.
Hops? What's hops?
It is a flavour which decides whether
it's a strong beer or a light beer.
Hey Arya, what are these lights, heat,
these plants? What's all this setup?
Basically, all the beer manufacturers
add artificial flavours in it.
But unlike them,
I made this set up to use plants
and use the natural flavours.
Because these plants grow only in
40 degree North Equatorial region
in a particular climatic
conditions and temperatures.
Alright, but how do they grow in our room?
That's why I've arranged this setup
of lighting and a certain temperature.
We are recreating those conditions
with this setup over here.
The step 4 is
We have to take the liquid mixed
with hops into the third container
and cool that with a chiller.
Oh!
The step 5 is to add yeast in that.
Yeast is the good bacteria.
The one which you said on that day
regarding the bacteria for making bread.
Yes, that one.
This helps for the fermentation.
We add curd in milk to make curd, right?
That's called fermentation.
Similarly,
this yeast converts that liquid into beer.
The end product which we get after
refrigerating is nothing but our beer.
[explodes]
-Oh no!
-Damn!
Hey, pour the water.
[fire dowsed]
[coughs]
Hey, why did it happen like this?
It's normal dude.
Let's do it again from the beginning.
It'll be done.
Hey, listen to me. Today isn't a good day.
Let's start tomorrow with a fresh mind.
Nothing bad would happen, it'll
be done. We started it, right?
I don't understand
anything, I'll be outside.
-We'll do it tomorrow morning.
-Dhruv, listen to me
Let's go to the hospital to meet Chey.
-Dhruv.
-Come dude.
Hey... Make sure that there aren't
any blasts or nothing of that sort.
Hey, nothing will happen to us.
-Hey Bunty
-Yes
Where did you park my black Mercedes?
Look there, dude
Yes, behind my red BMW
Hey, get that quickly.
I have to go to America.
Okay, we'll go.
"If the pin pierces you,"
"it's my mistake"
"My heart fell for it"
Nurse, why are my eyes are
getting red when I drink?
Give up drinking.
[chuckles]
-Is it painful dude?
-No.
I got adapted to repeated piercing.
Hey...
Nothing happens to me, right?
Hey, nothing will happen dude.
Hey, what'll happen to you dude?
We're here right?
-Hey, slowly
-Nothing will happen.
I have an important
client meeting at the office.
The delegates arrived from the US,
so I am unable to come to Hyderabad.
Damn! What's this client meeting dude?
She's been torturing me
by saying the same thing.
Hey, she won't come to Hyderabad at all.
-What are you crying for?
-Hey, stop it dude. You...
Hey, I have no one for me.
At least, you be happy
with your girlfriends.
Drunk lover is here.
Hey, you're important to us
Well, what's the mess of the girls?
Leave it
We shall be happy, come on.
-What, being handsome like you?
-Yes
[cicadas critter]
[explosion]
[music]
[burbling]
[pouring]
What's with him, dude?
Hey, he has prepared the beer.
Wake him up.
Hey Arya...
Arya...
Get up dude.
[stretching]
Hey, you made beer?
I tried something dude.
-Bro, you are great.
-Hey, get that stool.
How is it dude?
Super!
Hey, we shall three do it together.
Hey, we'll like our beer anyways
-Let's make some outsider drink it.
-We will do that. What's in that?
-What's this dude?
-Beer
Then, why are you staring
at the beer like an owl?
It's great.
[cheering]
I think God loves humans very much.
That's why he sent ambrosia in the
form of beer for everyone to be happy.
Hey dude, this is the right time
to take our beer to the next level.
Yes dude,
we should start selling our beer.
Let's sell it online.
We can have door delivery system
-It is a crazy idea.
-It is simply superb!
-Hey, the thing is...
-Hello... Hello.
There's hell lot of process for that.
We shall first create the logo,
then create e-commerce
website and make beer-bottling...
Hey, we can make that beer-bottling.
There's my uncle's godown
in Boduppal, right?
If we procure in a bulk way, we can
get an empty bottle for 2 rupees.
It's crazy, dude.
Let's get the website done online.
It'll be done in 5000 rupees.
By the way,
what shall we name this?
Kaboom... is what we shall name it.
What does it mean?
Kaboom means explosion, bang!
Those drinking our beer should forget
frustrations, tensions and everything.
They should get their minds blasted.
Wow, what a name!
Right, dude.
Even our beer
experiment started with a blast.
Yes!
[music]
-Hey Arya.
-Yes.
-Let's make a crazy Ad.
-Why?
Because the public should
know about our beer, right?
Right, isn't it? Then, we
shall film with the white guys.
Why do we need white guys?
Our guys believe to
whatever the white guys say.
[laughs]
Let's do it.
Rasikaraja Productions, Kaboom Ad,
scene 1 , take 1!
[eagle squeals]
[horse neighs]
[sighs]
Hey, what happened?
I can't walk anymore.
-What shall we do now?
-I don't know.
[eagle squeals]
[pops]
Drink Kaboom beers and feel like heaven.
Why didn't we get even
a single order, dude?
That's why I said not to
do an Ad with that black guy.
Hey idiot, he is the one
we found within our budget.
Maybe the people are thinking that
we shot that Ad in Mehdipatnam.
[message notification tone]
-Hey, we got an order.
-We got the first order.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Come on, note down the address.
-Note it down.
"Kaboom"
"A chilled beer is the one
which soaks your throat"
"We'll reach you and deliver
the beer at any time"
"Have the beer and we'll
ensure that you'll be happy"
"Give the order, this is the best deal"
"We got the milling"
"We got the mashing"
"We got the feeling"
"It's the Kaboom beer"
"We got the milling"
"We got the mashing"
"We got the feeling"
"It's the Kaboom beer"
"You'll leave your car if
you sip one drop of our beer"
"There are no problems
associated with our beer"
"Our store is unlike those
which sells in black"
"Stop going out and order it online"
"What's the price of the beer?"
"Hundred bucks"
"What's the taste of the beer?"
"Super... Duper"
"What's the price of the beer?"
"Hundred bucks"
"Say cheers and tell how does it taste"
"Super... Duper"
"Come on, have a chilled beer"
"Don't you care anything on weekends"
"Have Kaboom beer and sway"
"Wait, you'll get it"
"We got the milling"
"We got the mashing"
"We got the feeling"
"It's the Kaboom beer"
"We got the milling"
"We got the mashing"
"We got the feeling"
"It's the Kaboom beer"
"You'll leave your car if
you sip one drop of our beer"
"There are no problems
associated with our beer"
"It's the Kaboom beer"
-Hey
-What?
-Money [laughs]
-Hey
-How much dude?
-Wait, I'll say
Dude, tell the amount?
[cupboard opens]
Cheers!
Hey crazy dude...
All the money required for
Chey's treatment is arranged
First thing in the morning,
we shall go to the hospital and pay money.
-Done
-Okay
Done
-Kaboom.
[knocking]
Hey wait, I'm coming
The beer is out of stock, come tomorrow.
[camera clicks]
We're from the excise department
and you guys are under arrest.
For what?
For brewing beer illegally and selling
it to the people without a license.
Hello, this is legal in Europe, ok?
Officers seize.
We're seizing everything.
Go and get the beer samples
-Sir...
-Hello.
-Sir... Sir, there's nothing
-What are you doing?
-Sir, don't touch sir.
-Sir, don't do anything. Please
Sir, we took great pain to set it up.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you taking the system?
Sir..
Sir, they are wheat and
what'll be in that?
[splash]
Constables, check all their pockets
and take the phones. [camera clicks]
-Sir... There's nothing
-Show your pockets.
-Phone Sir...
-Take the phone
What'll be in the phone Sir?
Hey Arya
Hey, what keys are these?
Sir, they are my bike keys.
Hey, will bike keys be like this?
-Hey, check it.
-Sir, really bike keys.
Dhruv, Dhruv...
What sir,
let's go upstairs and have a talk.
-Hey, move
-Sir, there isn't anything there
Sir, there's nothing
-Nothing Sir
-Sir, there's nothing.
-Nothing, sir.
Sir, that's the money
for our friend operation.
Sir, that's the money for our
Chey's operation. Please Sir
-Seize the money.
-Sir...
money for our Chey's operation.
-Sir, please...
-Please believe us, sir.
Please sir...
[indistinct voices] [camera clicks]
[camera clicks]
[indistinct voices]
[indistinct voices][camera clicks]
-What about Chey's operation now?
-That's what I'm unable to understand.
'When everything was going well, there
was a big blow making recovery difficult.'
Hello...
Yes... Yes...
We need money for our son's operation.
We aren't getting money
despite asking everywhere.
You should somehow help me
If not, he won't live. Please...
Please help me somehow.
Hey, are you the police or rented goons?
To hell with your lives, rascals.
Open it, I didn't drink.
Your meter is wrong.
Uff... Here, check
Uff... Here, smell it.
I didn't drink, guys.
Oh no, I didn't drink.
Somebody get me a bail, man.
Hey Khaki shirt! Are you SI or CI,
what are you? Hey!
What brothers, what happened?
Why are you brought here?
-We made beer
-You made beer?
All make it and drink.
Is that wrong too? What justice is this?
Hello!
You deaf idiots, I'm talking to you.
Leave that, you look stylish
with a dog tag on your neck.
Why did they push you in?
That's a very big story brother
No problem bro,
we have time for the whole night. Tell it
"My name is Raj, sharp in studies."
[camera clicks]
"While in B Tech,"
"I had the wish to cook all new dishes,
feed everyone and become a master chef"
"I had great hopes but software job came
in between and shattered all the dreams"
"Shattered!"
"My life is shattered"
"Hey, office in the glass building
and every face sitting in it"
"were all artificial smiles boss
and that scent smell ruined it all"
"My life is..."
"My life is shattered"
"It was great in AC and with girls around"
"Hitech colouring and heating up weather"
"Outings in weekends and dancing in pubs"
"Cocktail drinking without breaking"
"My life is shattered"
"The main torture has started
project file made the puncture"
"I'll ask Google mother for matter"
for making me "Employee of the
month and I'm the eighth wonder"
"Getting a thousand rupee coupon
in smile and boss kept it in my hands"
"Not knowing where to use,
I folded and kept that in my back pocket"
"My life is shattered"
"Red Bus App..."
"8 hours duty went into 12, 13 hours
Day and night are in the office"
"With Google mother's mercy,
when I did code with no errors"
"The testing guy made nuisance citing
the phone code to be inefficient"
"My mind spoiled and
brain went in circles"
"My blood got boiled"
"Go rascal, I don't need your
job, money and the torture"
"Screaming aloud I hit the smart phone
in hand to the ground with force"
"The cunning manager"
"came smiling again to me,
placed hand on my shoulder"
"And said
congratulations, you're promoted!"
"He made me a fool repeatedly
saying so again" [applaud]
"He cooled me down and
made me collapse back on the chair"
"Not understanding anything
went to my parents and said"
"Mom, I can't do this
job and will leave this"
She said, "Why do you say so dear, who's
giving a girl with no job these days?"
And said, "Get married dear,
everything will be good"
"They even got me married
while in that confusion"
"They arranged the first night matter
on the third day of our marriage"
"They arranged a new cot
and kept flowers and fruits"
"They sprinkled full perfume,
pushed me and bolted the door"
"I was at cloud none
with great excitement"
"Glass in the hands of wife feeling shy"
"I grab it and drank
the whole milk"
"I started the bed fighting
and played holy of kisses and love"
"While thinking everything was going
good my heart became depressed at once"
What happened brother?
What else would happen bro?
"Shattered!"
"My life is shattered"
"My life is..."
"While in worry, the doctor blasted
a bomb saying the count is decreased"
"My wife who understood
the matter jumped away"
"without even leaving a message
and closed our marriage shutter"
"My life is gone"
"The hope in the heart went rotten"
"The software blasted
in the mind. Shattered!"
That is my situation brother.
Even my wife left me and went away
I wish that even a Pakistani
shouldn't face these problems, bro.
You do what you like and don't get into
jobs thinking life should be secured.
Bro, they brought us here
for doing what we like.
Hey, you don't worry guys.
Laddu bro is there and he'll take care.
Don't worry
-Good morning, SI sir.
-Good morning.
Yes, Laddu bro's men have come.
These are Raj's bail papers.
Bro, they are our guys.
Bail them out too.
'In that way, Raj Bollam entered
into our lives like a cyclone.'
A bunch of city youth
attuned to merrymaking
came up with a new technique
of brewing beer to earn money
-and were caught by the cops
-Look at your hero.
selling them online.
Your wedding with Rahul
is just two months away.
-I don't want to marry Rahul...
-I don't want to listen to anything.
Get into your room. Go!
You've brought a bad name for our family.
Looks like your brother Shourya
will get spoilt because of you.
It's better that you leave the house.
-Hello
-Arya, did you go to jail?
Yes. So, what?
Idiot, why are you doing so?
My dad is threatening to
get me married to Rahul.
Good, marry him.
Damn!
[phone ringing]
You became very popular.
As I pampered being motherless,
your works have been so.
Where are you going son?
I'm getting bored being here daily, mom.
I'll go, meet friends for some time.
Not even one guy came and
visited you for so many days.
They'll have their own
tensions mom, leave it.
Are you understanding how
much tension I'm taking?
Take care of your health first, son.
Mommy, you don't take
any tension and be happy.
Nothing will happen to me. See,
I'll just go and be back immediately.
Okay? You don't take any tension.
Hey, why are you guys
taking me into the bushes?
Are you taking a good
care of my guy or not?
Is he any kid to take care?
He's moving around in the
house as if his own house.
He's been moving carefree in the house.
Why are you wearing a
jacket in the sun, dude?
No idea, but I'm feeling very cold.
And this Beanie?
I'm losing hair heavily
because of the treatment.
No problem dude,
everything would be alright.
How is our Mahishmati, bro?
It's like hell, move.
Surprise!
Go, bro.
What, should I go into that?
Am I a rat to scroll into that?
Either rats or we shall
go in this way, move.
-Oh no...
-Slowly
Are you shocked?
-Hey, why is everything bizarre here?
-Of course, it would be.
This is our beer factory, bro.
Kaboom!
Kaboom?
What's Kaboom?
Boom!
Any guy drinking should get banged.
Basically, an explosion.
So it would be that crazy.
Drink, come on drink bro.
Open it dude.
[fizzes]
Look, you too will go
blasted after drinking.
-Come on drink, bro.
-Nothing will happen, right?
You'll be alright.
Drink and see.
How is it?
You are spellbound, aren't you?
Kaboom?
I never had such a beer in my life dude
-Do you have some more?
-Do you want it?
-Get one more, don't waste time
-Hey, bring all the beers.
Come on, let's do a party.
-Let's make all sleep in a range. Move...
-Let's go.
[drumming]
"I got my mind into drinking you"
"When your foam flushed up,
I feel like blinking"
"I got my mind into drinking you"
"Hey...
I got my mind into drinking you"
"I got my mind into drinking you"
"It seems all those having
toddy would go to Kailash"
arrack move around in paradise."
"Hey baby Kaboom!
All those drinking you..."
"None of the humans would forget
you for their next seven lives"
"Lost my mind... I lost the mind over you"
"I got my mind into drinking you"
"Hey... Hoi!"
Hey, I wish to be the
same with you forever.
Hey, nothing will happen to you.
You'll be with us and you'll be good.
Listen to us.
Bro, tortures have gone high in our lives.
Yes bro, life has become very restless.
Hey, we shall do something.
Whatever it is,
we shall all do that together.
Obviously...
Hey... Whatever you do never
get into a corporate job like me.
We don't have such courage, bro.
-Hey, what exactly is life?
-What do you mean?
Define life in a single word.
Food
Beer.
Music
-Friends dude
-Wow! Well said, bro!
Hey, let's together
start a hangout place.
Friends like us should come there,
have great food, listen to good
music, have beer and enjoy greatly.
Crazy idea, dude!
Hey, this sounds great.
Hey, Chey will play live music.
And we got our own beer.
Hey, what shall I do then?
You are the chef, right?
You just made us great food.
-You cooked the food very deliciously.
-Yes
-Is it? Is it very delicious?
-Yes.
What did you wish to do
leaving that corporate life?
-To become a chef?
-To become that, right bro?
But, would I really be able to do that?
-Bro, who did all this?
-You did it in a very wonderful way, bro
Who did? Tell me, who did all this?
-Seriously, guys?
-Yes and you fix for it.
-Let's do it
-Say cheers. Say cheers!
-We shall make it phenomenal.
-Move, we shall do it for sure.
Hey, we shall now go legally
for Rest-O-Bar setup.
Yes, no one should point
fingers at us this time.
What all do we need for that?
-Liquor license.
-Food license.
Then, the location?
Not all those, money is the first and
the foremost thing that we need.
Hey patient, move aside.
Here is my salary slip and when
we keep these flat papers too,
we will easily get a loan from the bank.
You don't need to do this.
I'm doing it as I liked it.
If I do this job for one few more days,
you will immediately admit me
in Erragadda Mental Hospital.
Still, nothing is lost now.
I wish to enjoy my life
happily in my terms.
Super!
Then, I and Dhruv will go to the bank
with Raj's papers and apply for a loan.
I and Arya will search for locations.
-I am going to the office
-Bye
[traffic]
-It is good, dude.
-This place is crazy.
I liked it very much.
The location is easy to find
and it is on the main road.
We shall setup a
kitchen over there for Raj.
Bunty and Dhruv will
setup brewery here.
My dad fixed engagement for me
and Rahul on the 18th next month.
[mesage notification tone]
He is now taking me out.
I will make a setup of live music on
that platform which is on the left side.
-What happened, dude?
-Nothing.
Any problem?
-Where shall we put up live music?
-Over there.
[money rustling]
Sir, we are trying very sincerely.
We are going legally in all the aspects.
Somehow, facilitate to sanction
the loan, sir. Please, sir.
Okay.
Boys, papers are very clear.
We'll show these papers to the
advocate, take legal opinion
and finally, we will sanction
the loan with manager's approval.
How long would it take for all
this process to complete, sir?
All the papers are genuine.
It takes maximum one week, it'll be done.
One week?
Sir, please see that it's
done in one week for sure
-as my friend has an operation, sir.
-Yes, sir.
Boys, forget about loan.
You'll have the other things
right? Go and look into those.
-Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
Our beer is very famous in Hyderabad, sir.
You should taste that for sure.
Thank you so much sir, thank you.
Crazy dude! All our problems
will be solved if we get the loan.
We can get Chey operated.
Yes dude, he'll be normal again.
Hey, we can open Rest-o-Bar.
Hey finally,
even Raj can leave that torture job.
Hey, even before that we
shall repair Raj's Philanthar.
Philanthar?
Hey, pull over.
Let's smoke.
Bro, give two cigarettes.
Here, dude.
-Cheers
Hey, why is Geetha
going with someone else?
Hey, take the phone. Let's inform Arya.
[phone ringing]
Bro, you somehow talk to the owner
and look into reducing
the lease a bit, please.
It's difficult, bro.
Hey Arya, Geetha is moving
around here with some other guy.
Leave it dude.
She got engaged with another guy.
-What?
-Well, you leave that place.
-One more thing, don't tell to Chey
-Okay, we won't tell anything.
Hey, it seems Geetha got
engaged to that fellow.
Is it?
-Let's go and play with him.
-Come on.
Dhruv, you be right here.
I'll go and torture them
Go, dude.
Oh, wow! So cute!
[camera clicks]
Wow, super! Wow!
-Do you know this guy?
-Don't know.
Hey, wonderful framing dear
[camera clicks]
Hey, super!
Hey! Who are you rascal?
You're taking too many
photos like traffic police.
What dude, will you pay the challan?
Are you cooled down?
I was taking a selfie with the flag.
You don't know who I am?
Yes idiot, we don't know.
What'll you do?
Don't mess with me.
We'll go to the mess and have meals.
So what?
Looks like you've got no work.
Find some work.
-Shut up and get lost.
-Rahul, come. We'll go.
-Get out rascal
-Bugger off.
I'll look into you, guys
Something is on your pant,
first look at that.
-Chaitanya
-Yes
Hi, this is Priya
-Interior designer, right?
-Yes, Raj Bollam sent me.
Yes, he informed me
[music]
[pub music]
-Hello
-Hello sir, can you hear me?
Yes, tell me Raj.
Sir, I'm not liking this job Sir
What? Is food not getting digested?
Not food indigestion sir.
Job... I'm not liking the job, sir.
What, isn't the parrot flying?
What shall I do if your parrot
isn't flying, bloody idiot?
Not the parrot, you fool. Job...
I'm resigning to the job.
Are you designing a new project?
Oh my baby, cool! Do it.
-Junk is piling up here, rascal.
-Will you bunk? Is this a college to bunk?
-You mad idiot!
-What, a sweet potato?
Yes, sweet potato. Place that in your ear.
Did you say that you want
to take good care of me? Why?
Hey, what's taking good care of you?
You anaconda faced rascal
born on no moon day!
What, you came to Manikonda?
What for, dude?
I'm coming to do your final rites.
You want to bow to me?
Alright, come. Come and do it.
My baby, go on as you wish.
Hey rascal, I'll come and finish you.
Co... Is the code okayed?
My foot! Damn!
[mobile shatters]
[screams]
He said that the code is ready.
Where is he?
Hey Raj, didn't you say
that the code is ready.
To think creatively by
throwing us into a 4 x 4 box,
How do you think that it
would happen, you rascal?
Rascal?
You're fired.
Who the hell are you to
fire me, idiot? I'm leaving.
-Oh crap!
-Damn!
Raj, you're promoted.
Congratulations!
Fold and keep it in your pocket.
You shall serve two months
notice period, okay?
Do I have to serve two
months notice period?
Okay. Here is the first month
and this is the second month.
Oh man!
Die, you waste idiot!
He said he would take good
care of me, didn't he?
[music]
-Hey, what's this tattoo?
-That's a big story and I'll say it later.
We shall set the kitchen
in this North East.
[camera clicks]
Baby, all the works of Rest-o-Bar
works are going at a fast pace.
Hey, give that laptop.
-Hey, wait due. Why?
-Hey, give it here
Hey, give it here.
Hey, let me speak to Soumya.
Hey Soumya...
Hi...
-Give me just five minutes.
-Okay.
Hey, what're you doing?
I kept Raj's photo in a matrimony site.
Wow!
Hey, where are you taking me?
You wait bro, I'll set it out.
Hey, you guys have ruined my
life from the day you came.
What's this dude?
Where did you get me?
-What's this, dude?
-You come bro, nothing will happen
Who are those two people?
They look great, right bro?
They are his assistants.
What's this?
-Hail the Lord! May the troubles be gone
-What?
You wait bro.
[strange language]
What's his language dude?
What's all this, man?
[strange language]
Too much, bro.
[screams]
[strange language]
Bro...
[screams]
[groaning]
[laughs]
-Hey, my pant became tight
-Wow! Wonderful bro.
Salutes sir.
Celebrate now.
Bro, Sweet potato of Raj.
What's wrong dude?
I think I have seen this guy somewhere.
-We shall interchange right one to left.
-Bro.
We'll keep it simple.
Everything is ruined.
What's wrong?
I think I have seen this guy somewhere.
Geetha's finance dude.
That fellow?
Hey, he is buying condoms.
Bloody idiot, come on dude.
Hey, forget that girl.
It's tough to forget the girl
but everything is slowly settling.
What is settling, rascal?
For everything.
Hey, hit that rascal!
[vehicle alarms]
Hey, I'll make you forget
that girl permanently.
Hey, hit that rascal. Break his head.
-Security!
-Hit, come on one more hard.
Hey, who are you idiots?
-Leave idiot!
-Who are you, idiots?
-What is settling, rascal?
-Hey!
Not just in my bank but will see to
that you won't get a loan in any bank.
The point is, he is the manager for the
bank for which we have applied for a loan.
That fellow challenged us.
Not just this bank,
but he'll see that no other bank
in this city would give us a loan.
You idiot!
-You've ruined everything.
-Sorry bro, we didn't do knowingly.
-I hit my Manager and came believing you.
-Nothing happened bro.
-Hey, get lost!
-I didn't do it intentionally.
-You'll die in my hands.
-Bro, wait.
Hey, you wait bro.
-How about money for Chey's operation now?
-Hey! You first stop crying, idiot.
What's you with this
personality and crying? Damn!
Damn, no link to your shape and the
performance. It's a total disconnect.
You all together have damned me. Damn!
Hey Dhruv, don't cry.
Nothing will happen
to me and I'll be fine.
All of you go and...
Hey Dhruv, Dhruv!
[sobbing]
Don't cry, nothing will happen.
Bro, what shall we do now?
[sobbing]
Hey, all of you get out first.
All of you get out first.
[glass bottles clinking]
Believing you,
it's like I've put a bomb under my seat.
We worked hard and prepared Kaboom beer.
Damn!
Anybody drinking Kaboom beer for once,
would falling in line to
our website every day.
They used to order thrice a day.
Yes dude.
Were they drinking daily?
-Daily!
-Yes, bro.
You tasted the beer, right?
Don't you know?
Laddu bro.
-Who?
-Laddu bro...
It was him who arranged bail for you guys.
-Yes, he got us bail.
-Ok... ok.
We can Laddu bro for finance.
Yes, what else.
Bro,
we shall go and ask Laddu bro for finance.
Ahh! It isn't such a simple matter.
Why?
If we don't pay the monthly payment,
he will break the bones and use
the marrow as stuff for his drinks.
If we get even slightest
doubts on us and our ideas,
what all everyone said and
scolded will go real now.
It's like we are unfit for anything.
Do you know what is
the biggest risk in life?
It's not to take up any risk.
-We shall do.
-We will do bro.
-We will do bro, fix bro.
-Please bro, ask him.
-Fix?
-Fix bro.
[vehicle honks]
Hey, who allowed you inside? Security!
Call the security...
-I'll see who'll come?
-What do you want?
Get the file, idiot.
Which file? We won't give any files.
-Why do you say which files, rascal?
-Slap him.
-Give him one.
-You know who am I?
Why do say so, when asked for file rascal?
Hit, give one on the face hardly.
Sorry, sorry! Ok, what do you want?
Get the file.
-Ok?
-Yes, all are there and perfect.
-You...
Hey, if you either call
Geetha again or torture,
I will bury you right here.
-Then, my engagement?
-What, rascal...
What just engagement rascal,
she's the girl of our friend,
we'll take her away even if married.
-It's my ring, give it to me.
-Come on pull that out.
"Player: Palke Jhukau Tujhe Dil Me Basau
song being played from the film Saajan"
Go, get the money.
[glass bottles clinking]
-Hey, money came.
-See, money has come.
Money guys!
Handover to them.
-Thanks, brother.
-Right, brother.
-Ah!
-Let's move.
-Hello!
-Yes.
Monthly interest...
You know what happens if not, right?
Your bones will be gone, understood?
-Hey, come on bro. For sure.
-Sure.
-Go!
-Right brother, bye.
Please give two days time and I'll pay.
Madam, your two days is already gone.
We will have our rules right?
Please understand!
I'll give in two days.
No madam, we'll have our rules.
You'll have to pay
today and no chance now.
Aunty, once please...
Pay the money for Chey's treatment aunty.
-Take aunty.
Come on, you don't cry so aunty.
It'll be sweet only when you scold us so.
Yes aunty.
[weeping]
Don't worry aunty, Chey will get alright.
First you go and pay the money
Come on, pay the amount
Come on aunty, what's this?
[music]
Hey, come on guys...
Sir, when are you doing an
operation for my friend?
Doctor is coming from US in a few days.
But, I'm reminding you once again.
Success rate in this operation is just 5%.
So, it's good that you keep Chaitanya as
happier as possible before this operation.
Nice shades.
I bought them online just yesterday.
Oh..!
Your brothers came and
said great about you.
They're my family now.
If you are fine with it...
You and even your baby...
[music]
Hey, she should've come by 10 right?
Hey dude, she won't come. Take it easy.
[metal clinks]
Hey, when such a grand wedding is on
here why do you think about her?
Hey, you take it easy
dude, move. Come on, move.
Sorry...
Huh?
-Sorry...
-Say properly.
-Sorry.
-Say further better.
-Sorry, my dear.
-Ah!
Sorry...
-So, will you hit for me?
-I will kill.
Love you baby.
Your dad is sent you out nicely.
-Can I escape for loving you?
-No way out, then?
"Life is just one and
friendships are a boon"
"This moment is melting down,
make it a remembrance"
"If one falls down, won't they come?"
"When we are together,
the courage is built"
"Friendship not
having difficulty or loss,"
"Is the strength in you"
"Not leaving once it happens"
"This is the boon!"
"It is happiness with fun and excitement"
"It always is there in friendship"
"It is fun and excitement when we meet"
"It never has an end"
"Closeness putting away the hesitation"
"Dashes in either
requesting or threatening"
"Friendship annoying even when said no"
"It is the quality never leaving you"
"Will the smiles stop now in the four?"
"There won't be any sorrow now in the run"
"In the war of doing what's liked"
"Nothing comes a block in the heart..."
"This is the story of friendship"
"This is..."
"This the boon"
How was the taste, grandpa?
These aren't good, those made by
your mom are better than these.
Oh no, thank God you appreciated.
"It is happiness with fun and excitement"
"It always is there in friendship"
"It is fun and excitement when we meet"
"It never has an end"
"Fun and excitement..."
-Chey, hey Chey!
-Chey, what happened?
-Hey! Chey, hold him.
-Hey Chey, get up.
-Chey, hey Chey!
-Chey, what happened?
-Hey! Chey.
-Hey Chey, get up.
[beeps]
Memories of a person for
lifetime are given to me,
by my friends just in 27 years.
I don't have any regrets.
So, I can happily breathe my last.
We all shall be together
like this forever dude.
Hey, whatever problem we may get in life,
even if earthquake
comes or in any condition,
we should be together like this forever.
Promise.
[shouts]
Hey,
I wish to be like this with you forever.
-What is life?
-Friends, guys.
Wow bro, well said.
He's crying dude.
[sobbing]
Chey, don't cry dude.
-Come on man!
-Come on!
Nothing will happen, don't cry.
This was given to my dad when in
service as the best employee award.
He felt very happy when he received this.
-Chey, don't cry dude.
-Stay calm.
-Hey, don't cry.
-Don't cry, keep it down.
Hey, no problem, we'll play cricket well,
win many trophies and
make uncle feel proud.
-What do you say?
-Yes dude.
-Take it!
We will play cricket well, dude
-That's it?
-Yes, if needed I'll talk to your dad.
-Talk!
-Uncle!
You happily chill in Paradise
with no tensions having elixir.
We'll take care of Chey, ok?
Hey, not one by one but we all
three should take care of Chey together.
Yes
-Ok?
-I'll take care on Monday...
...Tuesday and Wednesday.
Then, I'll take care on
Thursday, Friday and Saturday.
-That's it!
-Hey! Damn!
Come on is only Sunday for me?
This is unfair,
I too will take care
of him for three days.
First, you take care of
your da not to hit on your back
and then you can take care of him.
-Is it?
-Yes idiot!
Hey! Hey!
"The happiness has taken holiday"
"and is going away"
"Our hearts are filled with tears"
"This is it... "
"A holiday... This is it"
[defibrillation]
"This is it"
"This is grief"
'The college in which we failed and
cited our ideology to be wrong,'
'has called us to give a
speech on Entrepreneurship.'
'We may fail in many exams in life,'
'but we passed in distinction from
the biggest exam God has given.'
'The name of that exam is life.'
'Life doesn't have surety. Anything
might happen in life at anytime.'
'So, as long as we are there, we should be
together with our friends and families...'
'by doing the work we like
and achieve what we want to,'
'playing, singing, even if we get in a
big difficulties or even if we face death'
'we should be supportive to each
other, laugh loudly and face that.'
'Finally, we shall live every
second of life completely'
'and fill our lives with
beautiful moments.'
'Because we can't take
anything while leaving this world...'
'...except the memories.'
[applause]